[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This German car brand was founded by August Horch in 1909.", "correct_answer": "Audi", "incorrect_answers": ["Opel", "BMW", "Smart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fictional USS Echo was commanded by Lieutenant Rip Crandall. Who was the first mate?", "correct_answer": "Tommy J. Hanson", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilbur F. Vandewater", "Warren Berlington", "Josh Davidson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plant, whose name in Greek means rose tree, is widespread in the Sino-Himalayan region and is the national flower of Nepal.", "correct_answer": "Rhododendron", "incorrect_answers": ["Datura", "Goldenrod", "Daisy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of flamingo are native to the Americas?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "2", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cats meet a pair of geese, Abigail and Amelia, on their journey in the movie The Aristocats. What is the name of the pairs uncle?", "correct_answer": "Waldo", "incorrect_answers": ["Arthur", "Gander", "Magoose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of grape, native to Europe, was devastated by a pest in the middle 1800s.", "correct_answer": "vitis vinifera", "incorrect_answers": ["vitis aestivalis", "vitis sylvestris", "vitis labrusca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the top speed that a Komodo Dragon can reach?", "correct_answer": "13 mph", "incorrect_answers": ["6 mph", "10 mph", "27 mph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is Virginia Falls located?", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["United States", "Austarlia", "Wales"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor said the following words: One must go to a bowling alley to meet a woman of your stature.?", "correct_answer": "John Gielgud to Liza Minelli", "incorrect_answers": ["Robin Williams to Sally Field", "William Shatner to Candice Bergen", "Burt Reynolds to Sally Field"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An eponym that describes a mens style is derived from the name of this Union general.", "correct_answer": "General Burnside", "incorrect_answers": ["General Sheridan", "General Tuxedo", "General Trouser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is NOT a myth about chocolate?", "correct_answer": "It is unsafe to feed chocolate to a dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Chocolate has no nutritional value", "Chocolate causes cancer", "Chocolate is rich in caffeine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Suppose Mr. Jones works with ANOVA, regression lines, the sign-test, and the Gaussian distribution. What field of mathematics does Mr. Jones work in?", "correct_answer": "Statistics", "incorrect_answers": ["Algebra", "Geometry", "Calculus"]}]